foxallamerica.com 2008-06-08

# FOX Sports on MSN - -

| 

** Fox Sports Interactive Media, LLC Privacy Policy **

Fox Sports Interactive Media, LLC.    ("FSIM") is part of the News America Group, which has adopted a set of Privacy Principles  available at  applicable to all its U.S.-based companies. Fox Interactive Media, Inc. operates the Internet Web site located at www.foxsports.com.     FSIM has implemented those Principles in this Privacy Policy, which describes how    we collect, use and share personally identifiable information ("PII") we obtain from and about individuals located in the U.S. FSIM operates general audience Web sites, and does not knowingly collect PII from children under 13 years of age.  From time to time FSIM may revise this Privacy Policy to reflect industry initiatives or changes in the law, our PII collection and use practices, the features of our Web sites or technology. If we make revisions that change the way we collect or use your PII, those changes will be posted in this Privacy Policy and the effective date will be noted at the beginning of this Policy.  Therefore, you should review it periodically so that you are up to date on our most current policies and practices  .     If FSIM materially changes its practices regarding collection or use of your PII, your PII will continue to be governed by the Policy under which it was collected unless you have been provided notice of and have not objected to the change. 

** COLLECTION: COLLECTION OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION ("PII") BY FSIM.  **

** General  ** . FSIM collects personally identifiable information ("PII" -- that is, information such as your full name, email address, mailing address or telephone number)  in order to create or enhance our relationship with you. When we collect PII from you it is because you are voluntarily submitting the information to us in order to participate in activities like sweepstakes, contests, games, surveys, forums, subscription registrations, in connection with content or suggestions you submit to us, chats or bulletin boards, or because you want us to furnish you with products, services or information.  obtain PII from  reputable 

** Cookies  ** . Cookies are small bits of information that the FSIM Web  sites place on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies remember information about your activities on our site(s) and enable FSIM to make your visits to our site(s) more enjoyable. For example, cookies can store your password for easy logon to a site you have previously visited, can save your preferences for a  personalized  home page or can track the items you have placed in your "shopping cart" during a visit to our online store.    Information about your activities on FSIM sites and other non-personally identifiable information about you may also be used to limit the online ads you encounter to those we believe are consistent with your interests. 

Third party advertisements displayed on  FSIM sites  may also contain cookie  FSIM does not control these  cookies and visitors to our Web site(s) should check the privacy policy of the  advertiser to see whether and how it uses cookies. See the "Notice" section below for more information on third party advertisements.  FSIM may use cookie  s and similar tools to relate your use of our Web site(s) to PII obtained from you or a reputable third party. For example, if you've asked us to provide you information about our upcoming products or promotions, cookie and/or click stream data  about your  activities  may allow us to limit the materials we provide you to items we think you will find interesting, based on your prior online activities and preferences. However, if FSIM wishes to combine your personal and cookie or click stream  information in this manner, we will obtain your express affirmative  consent.   

You can program your computer to warn you each time a cookie is being sent or to refuse cookies completely. However, without cookies you may not have access to certain features on News America Group's Web site(s), such as the Fox Movie Channel Backlot. 

** NOTICE: FSIM WILL PROVIDE YOU WITH NOTICE ABOUT ITS PII COLLECTION PRACTICES  **

When you voluntarily provide  PII to  FSIM, we will make sure you are informed about who is collecting the information, how and why the information is being collected and the types of uses FSIM will make of the information.    At the time you provide your PII, FSIM will notify you of your options regarding our use of your PII, including whether we will share it with outside companies (See "Choice" below).  This Policy describes the types of other companies that may want to send you information about their products and services and therefore may want to share your personal informatio  (See "Use" below). 

Sometimes we collect PII from consumers in manual forma  such as a post card or subscription form. Providing detailed notice in those situations often proves impractical, so consumers will instead be provided with a short notice that describes how to obtain the full text of this Policy and other relevant information from us. 

FSIM's Web site(s) may be linked to Internet sites operated by other companies. Some of these third party sites may be co-branded with the logo of FSIM or an affiliated entity, even though they are not operated or maintained by FSIM (for example, the co-sponsored chat pages, or advertising sponsor pages). FSIM's Web site(s) also carry advertisements from other companies  . FSIM is not responsible for the privacy practices of Web sites operated by third parties that are linked to our  sites or for the privacy practices of third party or  national Internet advertising companies. Once you've left a FSIM site via such a link or by clicking on an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party or advertiser site to determine how they will handle any PII they collect from you. 

FSIM's Web site(s) may also be linked to sites operated by companies affiliated with FSIM    (i.e., that are part of the News America Group). Although all News America Group entities adhere to the group's Privacy Principles located at  http://www.newscorp.com/privacy.html,  visitors to those affiliated sites should still refer to their separate privacy policies and practices, which may differ in some respects from this Policy.   

Some of the advertisements that appear on FSIM's Web site(s) are delivered to you by national Internet advertising companies such as Doubleclick and 24/7Real Media. These companies  utilize certain technologies to deliver advertisements and marketing messages and to collect anonymous information about your visit to our sites, including information about the banner ads they display, any cookie they place on your computer and your IP address. To opt out of information collection by these companies, or to obtain information about the technologies they use or their own privacy policies, please visit: 

** CHOICE: FSIM WILL PROVIDE YOU WITH CHOICES ABOUT THE USE OF YOUR PII **

FSIM will provide for purposes different from the purpose for which it was submitted  that are not affiliated with FSIM (i.e., not part of the News America Group) on. 

** USE: FSIM'S USE OF PII **

FSIM will use your PII  in a manner that is consistent with this Policy  FSIM  may share your PII with companies that are affiliated with us, that is, are part of the News America Group of companies  .  _ n,  _ FSIM may also share your PII with  that are not affiliated  with FSIM, but would like to send you information about their products and services. For example, some of the companies who supply prizes for FSIM's contests may have special offers or promotions that might be of interest to users of the FSIM site. However, you will always have the opportunity to instruct us not to share your information with third  partie  FSIM employees, agents and contractors must have a legitimate business reason to obtain access to your PII.  contractors or agents who help us manage our information activities (i.e., sweepstakes administration, order fulfillment, statistical analyses  )  may only use PII to provide FSIM with a specific service and not for any other purpose. 

FSIM may also enter into agreements with outside companies that possess the technology that allows FSIM to customize the advertising and marketing messages you receive on our Web sites.    Your non-PII and click stream data about your activities on our sites may be shared with these companies so this customization can be accomplished.    These companies will not share your information with any third party or use it for any other purpose.    Anonymous click stream and demographic information may also be shared with FSIM's advertisers and business partners. 

There may be instances when FSIM may disclose PII without providing you with a choice in order to protect the legal rights of FSIM, other companies within the News America Group or their employees, agents and contractors; to protect the safety and security of visitors to our Web sites; to protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or to comply with the law or legal process. In addition, if FSIM sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, FSIM may transfer your PII to a third party as part of that transaction. 

** SECURITY: FSIM PROTECTS THE SECURITY OF PII **

FSIM uses reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard PII in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. In addition, FSIM uses reasonable methods to make sure that PII is accurate, up-to-date and appropriately complete. 

** ACCESS: HOW TO ACCESS, CORRECT OR DELETE YOUR PII  **

FSIM has implemented    procedures for you to access, correct or delete your PII  . 

To access your PII, send an e-mail with the word "Privacy" in the subject line toFIMPrivacy@fox.com, or write to the FSIM Internet Privacy Information at Fox Sports Interactive Media, LLC. Business and Legal Affairs, 407 N. Maple Drive, Beverly Hills, California 90210, requesting a listing of the PII that is on file that you have provided or that has been obtained from a third party. FSIM will provide you with a list of your PII within thirty (30) calendar days from receipt of your request. There may be certain instances when FSIM may not be able to provide the PII, such as when access would violate the privacy of another individual orwhen access is prohibited by law.

There may be certain instances when FSIM may not be able to provide the PII, such as when access would violate the privacy of another individual orwhen access is prohibited by law. 

In the event the PII on file is incorrect, you may correct the PII by sending a written request for correction to FSIM Internet Privacy Information at Fox Sports Interactive Media, LLC., Business and Legal Affairs, 407 N. Maple Drive, Beverly Hills, California 90210, including  all of the incorrect PII  , (2) the corrections that you wish to make to your PII, an  d (3) your signature authorizing such changes. FSIM will then correct the PII in its database and send a written confirmation to you within forty-five (45) business days. 

If for any reason you wish to stop all future communications from this site, you may send an e-mail with the word "Privacy" in the subject line to  FIMPrivacy@fox.com,  o  r write to    FSIM Internet Privacy Information at Fox Sports Interactive Media, LLC., Business and Legal Affairs, 407 N. Maple Drive, Beverly Hills, California 90210, requesting that your PII be permanently removed from this site's database. FSIM will send a written confirmation of such removal to you within thirty (30) calendar days of receipt of your request.  _ E  _ -mails sent to    FIMPrivacy@fox.com  for purposes other than communication about PII may not be acknowledged or responded to. 

** REMEDIES AND COMPLIANCE: HOW TO CONTACT FSIM ABOUT PRIVACY CONCERNS **

If you have concerns regarding privacy, your use of the FSIM Web sites, or the collection and use of PII, you may contact the following FSIM representative: 

Privacy Liason 

Fox Sports Interactive Media, LLC. 

Business & Legal Affairs 

407 N. Maple Drive 

Beverly Hills, California 90210   
Telephone: (310) 969-7192   
e-mail:  FIMPrivacy@fox.com 

You may also request a written response to your concerns, which will be made no later than thirty (30) days after you contact FSIM.    ** **

|
